stargateworlds.com 2008-07-08

# Stargate Worlds :: Privacy Policy

Firesky, LLC. (together with its successors and assigns, " **Firesky** ," the " **Company** " or " **we** ") respects the privacy of its online visitors and recognizes the importance of protecting personal identifying information when you visit any web sites owned, operated, licensed or controlled by Firesky or its parent, Cheyenne Mountain Entertainment, Inc. (collectively, the " **Firesky Sites** ").  This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information you provide to us, and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the Firesky Sites, and any of our products and services (collectively, the “ **Services** ”). This Privacy Policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our visitors' needs. Access to and use of any Firesky Sites and Services is available only to individuals who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law. If you do not qualify, you may not use the Firesky Sites and Services. If you are a minor under the age of 13, you are not authorized to register, become a member of the Firesky Sites and Services or participate in features of the Firesky Sites and Services that require registration. If you are a minor between the ages of 13 and 18, you may register, become a member of the Firesky Sites and Services, or participate in features of the Firesky Sites and Services that require registration only in conjunction with your parent's or legal guardian's consent as further set forth below. We urge supervising adults to actively oversee minors' online use. 

This Privacy Policy addresses all aspects of our data collection and handling practices, including:

  * [Methods by which you may access and amend your personal identifying information](http://community.stargateworlds.com/privacy/#access)
  * [Methods by which you may ask questions or file complaints regarding our collection or usage of personal identifying information](http://community.stargateworlds.com/privacy/#ask)
  * [The consequences of an individual's refusal to provide information](http://community.stargateworlds.com/privacy/#refusal)

#### WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED? 

Firesky collects personal information from its online visitors on a voluntary basis and only in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. We may collect personal information from you in connection with your participation in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, and in connection with chats or bulletin boards, or because you want us to furnish you with Services or information. Personal information collected may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail address, phone number, fax number, home address, billing address, credit card information, and age. 

#### HOW IS THE INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?

Firesky collects personal identifying information via conventional internet forms. New visitors to the Firesky Sites may be asked to register. We may request specific details, which may include your name, phone number, fax number, and home address. This information will then be associated with your e-mail account, so that you may identify yourself during future visits to the Firesky Sites. .

#### COOKIES:

Certain sections of the Firesky Sites may use "cookies." Cookies are very small data files left on your computer by the Firesky Sites. These files can then be accessed by the Firesky Sites in the future. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. Please contact your PC consultant if you need additional information on cookies.

We may use web site browser software tools such as cookies and web server logs to gather information about our Firesky Sites users' browsing activities in order to constantly improve our Firesky Sites and better serve our visitors. This information assists us in designing and arranging our Firesky Sites in the most user-friendly manner, and in continually improving our Firesky Sites to better meet the needs of our visitors and prospective visitors. 

#### INFORMATION USAGE AND DISTRIBUTION:

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities and making available other products and services to our visitors and prospective visitors. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our CMS Sites and Services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our standards and those of our service provider, which are designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our visitors' personal information. 

**Advertising on the Site**

From time to time you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on our Firesky Sites. We take measures to select product or service providers that are reputable. However, we cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies. 

**Sharing Information**

Although we do not currently share any information you submit, by submitting your e-mail address and other information, you understand that we may enter into strategic marketing alliances, partnerships or agreements with third parties who may be given access to personal information you have provided to us, including, but not limited to, your name and email address, for the purpose of providing you with information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you or for other business services. In connection with any such arrangements, we will generally retain ownership over all information provided by our users on the Firesky Sites and via the Services. In addition, we will NOT share information regarding your personal financial data or Social Security number, if the same has been collected. By using the Firesky Sites, you agree to allow such sharing of your personal information with third parties and you further waive any claims that could be made against us in relation thereto.

**Transfer of Business Assets**

In the event that Firesky undergoes a change of control or is sold or transferred, or in the event that substantially all of its assets are sold or transferred to a third party, the Firesky Sites, Services, and any personally identifiable information collected by Firesky, will be among the transferred assets. By using the Firesky Sites, you hereby agree and consent to such transfer or assignment of your personal information collected by Firesky or to a change of control of Firesky, and you further waive any claims that could be made against us in relation thereto.

**California** **Privacy Rights Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83**

If you are resident of California, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request certain information regarding Firesky’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [legal@firesky.com](mailto:legal@firesky.com) or write us at: Firesky Privacy Policy, Firesky, LLC, 4140 East Baseline Rd., Suite 208, Mesa, Arizona 85206.

#### DATA SECURITY:

We use reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard your personal information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, we also use reasonable methods to make sure that your personal information is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.

#### ACCESSING YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION:

_Opt-out provision:_

If you do not want Firesky to send you e-mail or postal mail about our Services, you can opt out at the time of registration or information collection, or at any time in the future by contacting Firesky by e-mail at [legal@firesky.com](mailto:legal@firesky.com) or by mailing a request to: Attn: Firesky Privacy Policy, Firesky, LLC, 4140 East Baseline Rd., Suite 208, Mesa, Arizona 85206. By using the Firesky Sites, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you are not authorized to use the Firesky Sites. We reserve the right to make changes in this Privacy Policy, provided that we give notice to you of any such changes. Please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any such notices of changes in our privacy practices. Your continued use of the Firesky Sites will signify your acceptance of these changes. 

#### IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS OR COMPLAINTS REGARDING OUR COLLECTION OR USAGE OF PERSONAL IDENTIFYING INFORMATION:

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact Firesky by email at [legal@firesky.com](mailto:legal@firesky.com) or by writing to: Attn: Firesky Privacy Policy, Firesky, LLC, 4140 East Baseline Rd., Suite 208, Mesa, Arizona 85206. 

#### IF YOU REFUSE TO PROVIDE INFORMATION ONLINE:

Firesky does not require registration or submission of personal identifying information to obtain basic access to the Firesky Sites; however, you may not be able to access all areas and functions of the Firesky Sites. 

#### PUBLIC FORUMS:

Firesky may make chat rooms, job listing areas, message boards, news groups, and other community Services available to you on the Firesky Sites. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Firesky has no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal identifying information or any other information about yourself. The information presented in these areas reflects the views of the individual users or hosts and does not necessarily reflect the views of Firesky or any of its affiliates.

#### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY:

The Firesky Sites comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. 

**Children under the age of 13**

Because the Firesky Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13, Firesky does not provide memberships or registration to persons under age 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may not create an account on the Firesky Sites, you may not sign up for or participate in any Service, or buy anything through the Firesky Sites, and you are not eligible to enter any of Firesky's sweepstakes or promotions. Except as may be required by law, Firesky will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any personal information from children under the age of 13.

**Children between the ages of 13 and 18**

If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please let your parent or guardian know about this Privacy Policy and get his or her permission before you give us any of your personal identifiable information, before you use any of our message board, instant message or chat features, before you sign up or participate in any Services, and before you buy anything from the Firesky Sites. Do not post your real name on a web site or message board, and never tell anyone online anything private about yourself or your family, including your phone number and address. Use screen names at all times. If you win a sweepstakes that has a prize, your parent or guardian will have to mail or fax us a signed note at the address or fax number listed in the rules for the specific contest that says it was OK for you to enter, and tells us they will accept the prize for you. Some areas of the Firesky Sites may have special rules for children under the age of 18. When you are in those areas, you must follow those rules.

**Information for Parents/Guardians**

Firesky encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on the internet, including Firesky's online games. Parents and guardians should regularly oversee their children's use of e-mail and other online communications and transactional features. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers that can help provide a safe online environment for kids.

If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child has submitted his or her personal information without your permission or consent, we will take reasonable steps to promptly remove that information from our database at your request. To request removal of your child's information, please send an e-mail to [legal@firesky.com](mailto:legal@firesky.com) and be sure to include in your message the same user name, password, and email address that your child submitted.

#### LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES:

The Firesky Sites may from time to time contain links to third-party web sites. Firesky is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a certain third party, you may contact them directly or visit their individual web sites to learn more about their individual privacy policies.

#### GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE:

The terms of this Privacy Policy are incorporated into our general Terms of Service. Please review our Terms of Service [Terms of Use](http://community.stargateworlds.com/tou/).

Last updated: April 15, 2008.
